[{"question": " do you realize this is probably the last time we&#146;ll all be here in the coffee house as six single people?", "answer": " why?! what&#146;s happening to the coffee house?!  oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yep! from now on its gonna be the four of you guys and me and the misses. the little woman. the wife. the old ball and chain.", "answer": " old?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " the young hot ball and chain.", "answer": " that&#146;s much better.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oh, where are you guys going?", "answer": " we&#146;re gonna pick up the wedding dress then we&#146;re gonna have lunch with mom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " ah. joey you&#146;re-you&#146;re having lunch with my mom?", "answer": " no, i-i just heard lunch. but yeah, i can go. sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  y&#146;know what? actually i&#146;m kinda glad they&#146;re leaving &#145;cause uh, i need to talk to you about something.", "answer": " what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well this uh, this may be a little awkward.", "answer": " listen, if you want to borrow money, its kind of a bad time. i&#146;m buying dinner for 128 people tomorrow night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " no, its&#133;its not that. umm, now what i&#146;m going to say to you, i&#146;m not saying as your friend. okay? i&#146;m-i&#146;m saying as it as monica&#146;s older brother.", "answer": " but you&#146;re still my friend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " not for the next few minutes.", "answer": " during this time&#133;are you, are you still my best man?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " nope.", "answer": " do i still call you ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " okay! you guys are getting married tomorrow and-and i couldn&#146;t be more thrilled for both of you, but as monica&#146;s older brother i-i have to tell you this. if you ever hurt my little sister, if you ever cause her any unhappiness of any kind, i will hunt you down, and kick your ass!  what? i&#146;m-i&#146;m-i&#146;m serious!  come&#151;hey! dude! stop it! okay? i&#146;m-i&#146;m not kidding here!", "answer": "  hey, i hear what your saying, okay? and, thanks for the warning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " no problem.", "answer": " so are we&#133;friends again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " okay.  you won&#146;t believe what monica&#146;s older brother just said to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " what &#145;cha doing mon?", "answer": " i&#146;m making a list of all the things that are most likely to go wrong at the wedding. now, that way i can be prepared.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " what are they?", "answer": " well, so far i have uh, my bride&#146;s maids dresses won&#146;t get picked up, my veil gets lost, or i don&#146;t have my something blue.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey! those are all the things i&#146;m responsible for!", "answer": " i had to go with the odds rach.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hey! you guys! remember that audition i had a while ago and didn&#146;t get the part?", "answer": " the commercial?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " that play?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " that other play?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " nooo!", "answer": " the movie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " yes!!", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " yes that&#146;s the one about the soldiers who fight in world war i!", "answer": " oh, yeah! back then y&#146;know, we called the great war. it really was!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " well anyway, the guy they wanted backed out and now they want me! i start shooting today!", "answer": " congratulations!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s great!", "answer": " wait! wait! wait! you can&#146;t start today! today&#146;s the rehearsal dinner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh no, i&#146;ll be done by then.", "answer": " oh. well then way to go you big movie star!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " i know! all right, i&#146;ll see you guys over there! i&#146;m off to fight the nazis.", "answer": " oh, wait joey! we fought the nazis in world war ii, not world war i.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " go ahead.", "answer": " you&#146;re gonna be late! go! go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " who did we fight in world war i?", "answer": " mexico?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yes! very good.", "answer": "  hey joey! we&#146;re ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah! me too.  the assistant director:  richard? we&#146;re ready for you.  joey tribbiani? this is richard crosby he&#146;s playing vincent.", "answer": " i&#146;m doing my scenes with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " nice to meet you joey.", "answer": " wow! i can&#146;t believe this! this is incredible. i mean you just won an oscar!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " no i didn&#146;t.", "answer": " i think you did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i think i lost. three times.", "answer": " uh&#133;cookie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  okay! we&#146;re about an hour away from getting the scene lit. so uh, if you guys don&#146;t mind, can we run it a couple of times?", "answer": " yeah, sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, all right. let&#146;s do it.  and&#133;action!", "answer": " we have to find the rest of the platoon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  what?!", "answer": "  the platoon is dead! face facts tony!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  so what are we gonna do?! we have no reinforcements! no-no food!", "answer": " no, we still have food in the basement! i saw potatoes and some dry pasta!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " hang on a minute! joey, you keep touching your face. is something wrong?", "answer": "  no. nope, i uh&#133;i th&#151;i thought it might be kind of a cool character thing. y&#146;know? he&#146;s uh, he&#146;s a face toucher.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think so. let&#146;s take it back to richard&#146;s last line.  action!", "answer": " we may not have any weapons, but we still have food. in the basement i saw potatoes and some dry pasta, and a few tins of tuna!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " honey, we gotta go!", "answer": "  okay. here&#146;s a question you never have to ask. my dad just called and wanted to know if he could borrow one of your pearl necklaces.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t have anything like that, but let me go see if rachel does.", "answer": " yes, include more people in this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " hey, do you realize that at this time tomorrow we&#146;ll be getting married?", "answer": " wait a minute! i have a date tomorrow night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " i just, i can&#146;t believe that we made it!", "answer": " well you don&#146;t have to sound so surprised.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry but&#133;nothing.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " well&#133;honestly ever since we got engaged i have been waiting for something to, to flip you out.", "answer": " honestly? me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah. y&#146;know i keep thinking that something stupid is gonna come up and i&#146;ll go all&#133;chandler. but nothing has.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " ohh, i&#146;m so glad. thank you so much for staying so calm during this. i mean it&#146;s really, it&#146;s made me stay calm.  i coulda been worse!", "answer": " okay. i&#146;ll be right there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " hey maureen!  gosh! hey uh, chandler? this is my cousin maureen.", "answer": " we&#146;re the bings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hi! oh you guys look so beautiful!", "answer": " mr. and mrs. bing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  wow monica! hey, just so you know i had my uh, older brother chat with chandler.", "answer": " what is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " mrs. bing? here, these are my parents umm, judy and jack geller.", "answer": "  it&#146;s lovely to meet you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  so are you his mother or his father?", "answer": " jack!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " what?! i&#146;ve never seen one before!", "answer": " dad! there&#146;s ross , why don&#146;t you go talk to him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t even have a chance to act as though i&#146;m okay with", "answer": "  hello all!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hi&#133;dad.", "answer": " hi mr.&#133;bing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " nora!", "answer": " charles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " it-it&#146;s so great to see you both here.", "answer": " yes! although, i think we may be seeing a little too much of some people. aren&#146;t you a little old to be wearing a dress like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " don&#146;t you have a little too much penis to be wearing a dress like that?", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " &#133;of course you can kick his ass son.", "answer": " you could kick anyone&#146;s ass you want too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, rach! rach! umm hey, could you do me a favor and would talk to chandler&#146;s dad and try to keep him away from chandler&#146;s mom?", "answer": " yeah! but i don&#146;t know what he looks like!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " he is the man in the black dress.", "answer": " man in the black dress&#133;   hi! i&#146;m rachel! i&#146;m a friend of monica and chandler&#146;s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " i&#146;m amanda.", "answer": " oh i get it! a&#133;man&#133;duh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  can i have everyone&#146;s attention please? i&#146;m uh; i&#146;m ross geller.", "answer": " doctor ross geller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " dad&#133;dad, please! as i was saying umm, i&#146;m dr. ross geller. uhh, and i&#146;m the best man. and uh, this marriage is doubly special for me umm, because not only is the groom my best friend but uh, the bride is my little sister. and, she&#146;s the greatest sister a guy could ask for. so if you&#146;d all please join me in raising a glass to the, the couple we&#146;re here to celebrate.  to the bings.", "answer": " to the bings!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " all right, i&#146;m gonna go steam my wedding dress okay? who wants the responsibility of making sure nothing happens to it?", "answer": " i&#146;ll do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " who wants it? anybody?", "answer": " i said i&#146;ll do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " nobody wants to do it? all right, i&#146;ll do it myself.", "answer": " monica! i&#146;m not gonna screw it up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? you&#146;re right, i&#146;m sorry. actually you were a big help tonight. yeah, and thanks for putting my grandmother in the cab and making sure she got to the hotel safely.", "answer": " well of course that is what i&#146;m here for!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " hey! where have you been?", "answer": " oh, taking my parents back to the hotel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " what? are you going back to work?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " nice shades.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " thanks. yeah, i figure if i wear these in my scenes at least i won&#146;t get spit in the eyes, y&#146;know?", "answer": " and if i remember correctly, ray ban was the official sponsor of world war i!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hey, where&#146;s chandler?", "answer": " uh, i think he&#146;s in rachel&#146;s room. see ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " is uh, is monica here?", "answer": " she&#146;s steaming her dress, why? what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " he left that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  tell monica i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": "  what&#146;s up?  tell monica i&#146;m sorry.  tell her yourself! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh my god! chandler just left though!", "answer": " yeah but, maybe it&#146;s not what we think. maybe it&#146;s tell monica i&#146;m sorry i&#133;drank the last of the milk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " or maybe he-he was writing to tell her that-that he&#146;s changed his name, y&#146;know? tell monica i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " i think it means he freaked out and left!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " don&#146;t be so negative! good god! isn&#146;t it possible that sorry is sitting in there  right now?!", "answer": " okay. phoebe, i-i think ross is right. what are we gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " look&#151;okay, i&#146;m just gonna&#151;i&#146;m gonna have to go find him and bring him back! okay? you-you make sure monica does not find out, okay?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " oh man! they-they just redid my make-up!", "answer": " just the last two pages.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " picture? what picture?", "answer": " could you uh, could you lower your script? i need to see your face so i can uh, play off your reaction.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " okay uh, look i know you&#146;re a great actor, okay? and you play all those shakespeare guys and stuff&#133;", "answer": " oh, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " but you&#146;re spittin&#146; all over me man!", "answer": " well of course i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " you know you&#146;ve been spitting on me?!", "answer": " that&#146;s what real actors do! annunciation is the mark of a good actor! and when you enunciate, you spit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": "  wow! didn&#146;t know that.", "answer": " great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " gunther have you uh, have you seen chandler?", "answer": " no. no, i haven&#146;t seen him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh damn!", "answer": " he&#146;s getting married tomorrow right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " yes. yes. don&#146;t worry. everything&#146;s fine. we&#146;ll uh, we&#146;ll see you tomorrow at the wedding.", "answer": " i wasn&#146;t invited.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " well then we&#146;ll-we&#146;ll see you the day after tomorrow.  mom?! dad?!  what-what&#133;what you guys doing here?!", "answer": " well you kids talk about this place so much, we thought we&#146;d see what all the fuss is about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i certainly see what the girls like coming here.", "answer": " why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  gunther?!", "answer": " your mother just added him to her list.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " what? your-your list?", "answer": " yeah, the list that&#151;of people we&#146;re allowed to sleep&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yes! no-no! i know, i know what the list is! mom! look if you see chandler, could you just let him know i&#146;m looking for him?", "answer": " and if you see rita moreno, let her know i&#146;m looking for her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " action!", "answer": " i found the picture!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " what picture?!", "answer": " the picture of my wife! in your pack!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " you went through my personal property?", "answer": " why do have a picture of paulette in your pack?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  because vincent, we were lovers.  for two years!", "answer": " cut! wonderful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " great scene yeah?", "answer": " oh you&#146;re awesome! and, in that last speech? you soaked me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " thanks a lot. the assistant director:  here&#146;s your call sheet for tomorrow.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m-i&#146;m not working tomorrow. the assistant director: you are now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  ross said there&#146;s still no word from chandler.", "answer": " oh man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh but he did say that they found the grandmother wandering down fifth avenue.", "answer": " okay. well there&#146;s one down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " y&#146;know she might not even notice he&#146;s gone.", "answer": "  i&#146;m gonna start getting ready!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " god! don&#146;t&#151;we can&#146;t let her start getting ready! this is too awful! oh god, but wait she&#146;ll be in the gown and then he won&#146;t show up and then she&#146;s gonna have to take off the gown&#133;", "answer": " shhh! stop it! stop it rachel! you can&#146;t do this here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry. i&#146;m sorry. it&#146;s just&#133;it&#146;s just so sad!", "answer": " yeah, but you&#146;ve got to pull yourself together! monica can&#146;t see you like this! then she&#146;ll know something&#146;s wrong!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " i know. i know. oh god.  there&#146;s no tissue! can you grab me some toilet paper?", "answer": " yeah.  oh, that&#146;s gone too. this is monica&#146;s bathroom right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " no-no! i-i&#133;i found one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh thank you!  oh god!  can i have another one?", "answer": "  sure.  do you need some floss?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " oh god i just can not imagine what is gonna happen if chandler doesn&#146;t show up!", "answer": " oh here&#146;s a whole bunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh, i mean she&#146;s gonna be at the wedding waiting for him and people will be whispering, &quot;oh that poor girl.&quot; y&#146;know? then she&#146;ll have to come back here and live all alone.", "answer": "  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " there was a pregnancy test in the garbage, and it&#146;s positive. monica&#146;s pregnant.  so i guess she won&#146;t be totally alone. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " i know! monica&#146;s gonna have a baby! hey, can this count as her something new?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " hey, do you think this is why chandler took off?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " no, she had to have just taken that test because i took out the trash last night.", "answer": " oh god, this is turning into the worst wedding day ever! the bride is pregnant. the groom is missing. and i&#146;m still holding this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " okay phoebe, we can not tell anyone about this.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " okay?", "answer": " yeah, okay. hey, wait. do you know what kind of birth control she was using?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " no. why?", "answer": " just for the future, this is hardly a commercial for it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " anything?", "answer": " no! i talked to joey on the set, he hasn&#146;t heard from him. i-i-i talked to chandler&#146;s parents again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " you told them he was missing?", "answer": " no! i made it seem like i was just calling to chat. pretty sure, they both think i&#146;m interested in them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " no! hey! hey! we can&#146;t!", "answer": " ross, she&#146;s gonna start getting ready soon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " well, can&#146;t you at least stall her a little? i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll go back to some of the places i went last night.", "answer": " all right, well how much time do you need?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " well how much time before she absolutely has to start getting ready?", "answer": " one hour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " give me two.", "answer": " then why do you ask?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " okay, wish me luck.", "answer": " okay. i&#146;m going with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": " ross, you&#146;re tired. you&#146;ve been looking all night. and clearly you suck at this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " all right, i&#146;ll see you guys later.", "answer": " okay. wait, do you know how you&#146;re going to stall her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " i&#146;ll figure something out.", "answer": " all right. good luck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " hey! okay, so i thought we&#146;d start with my make up and then do my hair.", "answer": " okay uh, but before you do that. i-i, i need you to talk to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " about what?", "answer": " umm&#133; i&#146;m never gonna getting married!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " yeah you will! the right guy is just around the corner! okay, are we done with that?", "answer": " no monica! i&#146;m serious! oh, maybe i should just forget about it. become a lesbian or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " any woman would be lucky to have ya.", "answer": " well maybe it would make me feel better if i slept with joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " excuse me, aaron?  hi! umm, i have a little problem with the schedules. originally, i wasn&#146;t supposed to work today, and i have this wedding that i really have to be at. it&#146;s my best friend&#146;s, and i&#146;m officiating so i really can&#146;t work past four.", "answer": " joey, you gotta stay until the end. we can&#146;t stop filming just for you. it&#146;s not like it&#146;s your wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " i&#146;m having surgery!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " yeah, i-i just made up the stuff about the wedding because i didn&#146;t want you to worry about me. but, i&#146;m having surgery today.", "answer": " what kind of surgery?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " transplant.", "answer": " but you&#146;re supposed to work on monday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " hair transplant.", "answer": " but you&#146;re not bald.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " it&#146;s not on my head.", "answer": " look joey, there&#146;s nothing i can do. besides, you&#146;re probably gonna be out by four anyway. we&#146;ve just got one short scene. it&#146;s just you and richard, and god knows he&#146;s a pro. you&#146;ll be fine.  morning richard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}, {"question": " hey! you&#146;re here! great! great! great! let&#146;s get going buddy, we&#146;ve got a scene to shoot!", "answer": " i&#146;m wearing two belts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " are you drunk?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " yes you are!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " we are never gonna find him! he&#146;s one guy in a huge city!", "answer": " oh my god! is that him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": " that is an old, chinese woman!", "answer": " he could be in disguise, y&#146;know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 341, "asentId": 342}, {"question": " so this is your office?", "answer": " how did you guys find me? i knew i should&#146;ve hid at the gym!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " what the hell are you doing?!", "answer": " panicking! and using the internet to try to prove that i&#146;m related to monica. how is she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": " she&#146;s fine. she doesn&#146;t know you&#146;re gone. and she doesn&#146;t have to know, okay? now come on, we&#146;re going home.", "answer": " no! no! no! i can&#146;t do that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}, {"question": " why not?!", "answer": " because if i go home, we&#146;re gonna become the bings! i can&#146;t be the bings!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 351, "asentId": 352}, {"question": " what&#146;s wrong with being the bings?", "answer": " the bings have horrible marriages! they yell. they fight. and they use the pool boy as a pawn in their sexual games!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 353, "asentId": 354}, {"question": " chandler, have you ever put on a black cocktail dress and asked me up to your hotel room?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " then you are neither of your parents!", "answer": " it&#146;s not just their marriage! i mean, look at yours. look at everybody&#146;s! the only person that can make marriage work is paul newman! and i&#146;ve met me; i am not paul newman. i don&#146;t race cars! i don&#146;t make popcorn! none of my proceeds go to charity.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": " but look chandler, right now, no one has a lower opinion of you than i do. but i totally believe you can do this.", "answer": " i want to. i love her so much, but i&#146;m afr&#133;it&#146;s too huge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 359, "asentId": 360}, {"question": " y&#146;know, okay. you&#146;re right. it is huge. so why don&#146;t we take it just a little bit at a time? okay? umm, forget getting married for a sec; just forget about it. can you just come home and take a shower?", "answer": " well yeah, but then&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 361, "asentId": 362}, {"question": "  yeah&#151;no-but-but-but-but! we&#146;re just gonna go home and take a shower. now, that&#146;s not scary right?", "answer": " depends on what you mean by we.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}, {"question": " the nights are the hardest.  but then the day comes! and that&#146;s every bit as hard as the night. and then the night comes again&#133;", "answer": "  the days and nights are hard! i get it! okay? look umm, rachel i&#146;m sorry! i have to start getting ready! i&#146;m getting married today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 365, "asentId": 366}, {"question": " i know. at dusk. that&#146;s such a hard time for me.", "answer": "  i&#146;m gonna go put my make up on, we have to be at the hotel in an hour!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 367, "asentId": 368}, {"question": " okay. but wait!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 369, "asentId": 370}, {"question": " let&#146;s go to lunch.", "answer": " i can&#146;t go to lunch!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 371, "asentId": 372}, {"question": "  what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " okay. all right.  honey listen. when i tell you what i&#146;m about to tell you, i need you to remember that we are all here for you and that we love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 377, "asentId": 378}, {"question": " okay, you&#146;re-you&#146;re really freaking me out.", "answer": " we can&#146;t find chandler&#133;&#151;&#145;s vest. we can&#146;t find chandler&#146;s vest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 379, "asentId": 380}, {"question": " how can that be?! oh wait! wait! are you, are you serious?!", "answer": "  found the vest! i mean we&#146;re gonna have to keep an eye on it, y&#146;know make sure we don&#146;t lose it again&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 381, "asentId": 382}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " oh wow! okay. don&#146;t scare me like that okay? i mean for a minute there i was like, &quot;oh my god! the worst has happened!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 383, "asentId": 384}, {"question": " i would sooner die in this hellhole then see her back with you!", "answer": " that can be arranged.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 385, "asentId": 386}, {"question": " let&#146;s reset.", "answer": " what?! he got me! owwwwww!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 387, "asentId": 388}, {"question": " let&#146;s take it from there.", "answer": "  are you a little off today? it&#146;s going terribly slowly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 389, "asentId": 390}, {"question": " look, my best friends are getting married in like an hour. okay? and i&#146;m the minister. please! please! can you pull it together?", "answer": " of course! i&#146;m-i&#146;m sorry. i-i&#146;d hate you to miss anything like that on account of me. i can do this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 391, "asentId": 392}, {"question": " thank you. thank you.", "answer": " still rolling, annnnd action!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 393, "asentId": 394}, {"question": " i would sooner die in this hellhole then see her back with you!", "answer": " now, that can be arranged!  slippery little bugger!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 395, "asentId": 396}, {"question": " oh my god monica!", "answer": " i wanna wear this everyday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 401, "asentId": 402}, {"question": " you look so beautiful.", "answer": "  i&#146;m so happy for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 403, "asentId": 404}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": "  hey! did chandler show up yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 405, "asentId": 406}, {"question": " yeah, we got him back. everything&#146;s fine.", "answer": " damnit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 407, "asentId": 408}, {"question": " what? why? where are you?", "answer": " i&#146;m still on the set!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 409, "asentId": 410}, {"question": " joey! the wedding is in less than an hour!", "answer": " i know! i&#146;m sorry! the guy&#146;s drunk, they won&#146;t let me go until we get this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 411, "asentId": 412}, {"question": " oh my god! i&#146;m gonna have to find another minister.", "answer": " no! no, i&#146;m the minister! all right, look-look, put &#145;em both on the phone, i&#146;ll marry them right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 413, "asentId": 414}, {"question": " ugh! joey, i have to go.", "answer": " hey! don&#146;t you hang up on me! i&#146;ll marry you and me right now! i have the power!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 415, "asentId": 416}, {"question": " there you go. you put on a tuxedo! now that wasn&#146;t so scary, was it?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 417, "asentId": 418}, {"question": " i&#146;m telling you, just a little bit at a time.", "answer": " yeah okay. well, what&#146;s the next little bit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 419, "asentId": 420}, {"question": " getting married.  okay. okay. you can, you can do that too! just like you&#146;ve done everything else!", "answer": " yeah. you&#146;re right. hey i-i can do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 421, "asentId": 422}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " okay, excuse me for a minute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 423, "asentId": 424}, {"question": " wh&#151;hey&#151;whoa-whoa, where, where you going?!", "answer": " ross, i am not gonna run away again! i just want to get a little fresh air.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 425, "asentId": 426}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 427, "asentId": 428}, {"question": "  wait! maybe, maybe you&#146;re overreacting! you do that y&#146;know.", "answer": " well phoebe, we gotta do something!  well, y&#146;know. i mean there&#146;s no way joey&#146;s gonna make it in time. so i&#146;m gonna through the hotel and see if there&#146;s any other weddings going on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 431, "asentId": 432}, {"question": " okay. oh but don&#146;t tell them monica&#146;s pregnant because, they frown on that.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 433, "asentId": 434}, {"question": " anastassakis/papasifakis wedding, excellent! {it&#146;s a good thing jennifer aniston is greek, because she had to pronounce those names. luckily for me, they were written on a sign.} congratulations.  mazel tov!  hi! oh, great hat.  listen umm, i need you to perform another wedding. can you do that?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. are they greek orthodox?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 437, "asentId": 438}, {"question": " hi!  hi!  hi. has umm, anyone seen chandler?", "answer": " i thought he was with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 441, "asentId": 442}, {"question": " he-he was with me umm, we&#146;re playing a little game, y&#146;know? hide and seek.", "answer": " you can&#146;t ask us son, that&#146;s cheating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 443, "asentId": 444}, {"question": "  you&#146;re right, thanks for keeping me honest dad.", "answer": " well, he better not come by here. he can&#146;t see the bride in the wedding dress.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 445, "asentId": 446}, {"question": " as i recall when we got married, i saw the groom in the wedding dress.", "answer": " but that was after the wedding, it&#146;s not bad luck then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 447, "asentId": 448}, {"question": " oh my god! monica!", "answer": " i know! hey, how&#146;s chandler doin&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 451, "asentId": 452}, {"question": " great. he&#146;s doing great. don&#146;t you worry about chandler.", "answer": " are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 453, "asentId": 454}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " well, you&#146;re-you&#146;re sweating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 455, "asentId": 456}, {"question": " these-these are beads of joy.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s sweet. don&#146;t touch me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 457, "asentId": 458}, {"question": " uh phoebe, can i see you for a second?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 459, "asentId": 460}, {"question": " what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " chandler&#146;s gone again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 461, "asentId": 462}, {"question": " aaron! you gotta let me go. the guy&#146;s hammered!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry joey, as long as he&#146;s here and he&#146;s conscious we&#146;re still shooting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 465, "asentId": 466}, {"question": " you wouldn&#146;t happen to have a very big fork?", "answer": " so i uh, i just talked to the director. that&#146;s it, we&#146;re done for the day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 467, "asentId": 468}, {"question": " well have we finished the scene?", "answer": " yeah! you&#133;you were wonderful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 469, "asentId": 470}, {"question": " as were you.", "answer": " so i got your car, it&#146;s right outside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 471, "asentId": 472}, {"question": " why? are we done for the day?", "answer": " that&#146;s what you told me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 473, "asentId": 474}, {"question": " no-no-no! we gotta go! come on!  here we go.", "answer": " is that my ass?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 477, "asentId": 478}, {"question": "  there he is!!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 479, "asentId": 480}, {"question": " hey! oh!", "answer": " you&#146;re not getting away this time mister! unless you want that ass kicking we talked about!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 481, "asentId": 482}, {"question": " hiiii-ya!!  i&#146;m serious! you&#146;re not walking out on my sister!", "answer": "  that&#146;s right! i&#146;m not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 485, "asentId": 486}, {"question": " then where the hell have you been?!", "answer": " i know about monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 487, "asentId": 488}, {"question": " you know?!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 489, "asentId": 490}, {"question": " yeah, i heard you and rachel talking.", "answer": " what?! what?! talking about what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 491, "asentId": 492}, {"question": " you don&#146;t know?", "answer": " know what&#151;if somebody doesn&#146;t tell me what&#146;s going on right now&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 493, "asentId": 494}, {"question": " what? you&#146;ll hi-ya?", "answer": " monica&#146;s pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 495, "asentId": 496}, {"question": " oh my god. oh my god! and you&#146;re-you&#146;re&#133;you&#146;re not freaking out?", "answer": " well i was! then i went down to the gift shop because i was out of cigarettes&#133; phoebe and ross: cigarettes?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 497, "asentId": 498}, {"question": " big picture please! so i was in the gift shop, and that&#146;s when i uh, saw this.  new york.) yeah, y&#146;know what? i thought anything that can fit into this, can&#146;t be scary.", "answer": " well you obviously didn&#146;t see chucky 3.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 499, "asentId": 500}, {"question": " but come on, look at how cute and small this is! so i got it to give monica so she&#146;d know i was okay.", "answer": " dude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 501, "asentId": 502}, {"question": " our little boy is getting married.", "answer": " oh look at you! so handsome!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 505, "asentId": 506}, {"question": " are you chandler?", "answer": " are you joey?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 509, "asentId": 510}, {"question": " huh. this is nice.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 511, "asentId": 512}, {"question": " oh i wish you&#146;re grandmother had lived to see this.", "answer": " she&#146;s right there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 515, "asentId": 516}, {"question": " not that old crow, my mother.  congratulations darling.", "answer": " i love you sweetheart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 517, "asentId": 518}, {"question": " not now.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 521, "asentId": 522}, {"question": "  who is this?", "answer": " i am father kalebasous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 523, "asentId": 524}, {"question": "  he&#146;s greek orthodox.", "answer": "  as are you&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 525, "asentId": 526}, {"question": " let us begin. dearly beloved&#133;", "answer": "  that&#146;s my line!  i can take it from here, thanks.  dearly beloved, i&#146;m sorry i&#146;m a little late. you may be confused by this now,  but you won&#146;t be memorial day weekend 2002. well, let&#146;s get started before the groom takes off again. huh?  we are gathered here today, to join this man and this woman in the bonds of holy matrimony. i&#146;ve known monica and chandler for a long time, and i can not imagine two people more perfect for each other. and now, as i&#146;ve left my notes in my dressing room. we shall proceed to the vows. monica?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 527, "asentId": 528}, {"question": "  he took off?", "answer": " go on! go on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 529, "asentId": 530}, {"question": " chandler, for so long i&#133;i wondered if i would ever find my prince, my soul mate. then three years ago, at another wedding i turned to a friend for comfort. and in stead, i found everything that i&#146;d ever been looking for my whole life. and now&#133;here we are&#133;with our future before us&#133;and i only want to spend it with you, my prince, my soul mate, my friend. unless you don&#146;t want to. you go!", "answer": " chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 531, "asentId": 532}, {"question": " you may not kiss the bride. so, i guess by the powers vested in my by the state of new york and the internet guys, i now pronounce you husband and wife. oh wait! do you take each other?", "answer": " i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 535, "asentId": 536}, {"question": " i do.", "answer": " yeah you do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 537, "asentId": 538}, {"question": " rings?", "answer": " aw crap! okay&#151;uh&#133;uh let&#146;s-let&#146;s do the rings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 539, "asentId": 540}, {"question": "  i love you. and i know about the baby.", "answer": " what baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 543, "asentId": 544}, {"question": " our baby.", "answer": " we have a baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 545, "asentId": 546}, {"question": " phoebe found your pregnancy test in the trash.", "answer": " i didn&#146;t take a pregnancy test.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 547, "asentId": 548}, {"question": " oh and they&#146;re gonna have a baby.", "answer": " uh-huh.   ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 551, "asentId": 552}]